chatandvision.com 2011-11-13

# Buy Skype Certifed Headsets, Phones, Webcams at ChatandVision - Skype Global Merchant Partner

|  |   
|  |  |  |  |    
---|---  
  
## CONTENTS

  1. WHY WE COLLECT
  2. WHAT WE COLLECT
  3. WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER
  4. SECURITY
  5. HOW WE USE COOKIES
  6. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
  7. PRIVACY QUESTIONS

|    
  
ChatandVision's Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by ChatandVision anytime you interact with ChatandVision, such as when visiting our website, purchasing products, or using our sales or support facilities. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our practices with regards to this, including what type of information we gather, how and for what purposes we use the information, to whom we disclose the information, and how the personal information is kept safe and secure. Your privacy is a priority at ChatandVision, and we do what we can to protect it.

ChatandVision may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 31 May 2010.

|    
  
## Why we collect

|   
We collect personal information because it helps us to deliver a customised customer service experience for you. This affords you convenient access to our product range and helps focus on categories most likely to interest you. In addition, your personal information helps allow us to keep you updated on the latest product announcements, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.  |    
  
## What we collect

|   
We may collect the following information: 

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

|    
  
## What we do with the information we gather

|    
The personal information may help us give you a better shopping experience with us in the following areas: 

  * we may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with a representative, making a purchase, or registering your product.
  * we may use the information to improve our product range and services offered.
  * we may send promotional emails (to the email address provided) about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting.
  * from time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
  * We will use the information to create an account area to which you can login and access your order history.

|    
  
## Security

|   
  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

ChatandVision takes your privacy very seriously. ChatandVision does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.

ChatandVision may share certain personal information with other companies with which ChatandVision have a strategic relationship and/or provide services on our behalf to your advantage. These companies may help process information, fulfil customer orders, deliver products, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess levels of interest in our product range, or carry out customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obliged to protect your personal information, except if exchange of information is required for your purchase. For example, when an extended warranty is purchased, you authorise ChatandVision and the Warranty Provider to exchange information to carry out the service. Without the exchange, it would be otherwise be difficult to have products purchased, customer service offered, feedback provided to us, or have access to special offers or content from ChatandVision.

We may also be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information if it is determined that it is necessary for security, law enforcement or other issues of public importance.

|    
  
## How we use cookies

|    
  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

|    
  
## Links to other websites

|    
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. |    
  
## Privacy Questions

|    
If you have any questions or concerns, you can email us at [support@chatandvision.com](mailto:%20support@chatandvision.com) with any requests. |    
Last updated 9th June 2010   
ChatandVision Limited. All rights reserved. |    
Back to Top |    
  |    

|  |
